// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "8+7 =",
    answer: "15",
    options: [
      "1",
      "15",
      "16",
      "12"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "5 âˆ’ 2 =",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "7",
      "1",
      "2",
      "3"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "24/2 =",
    answer: "12",
    options: [
      "24",
      "2",
      "12",
      "13"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "10 x 5 =",
    answer: "50",
    options: [
      "50",
      "15",
      "25",
      "100"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "If you had 10 bananas and a person gave you 10 more how much will you have altogether ?",
    answer: "20 bananas",
    options: [
      "20 bananas",
      "10 bananas",
      "70 bananas",
      "60 bananas"
    ]
  }, 
    {
      numb: 6,
      question: "If you had 20 cars and someone stole 3 of them how much would you have left ?",
      answer: "17 cars",
      options: [
      "11 cars",
      "16 cars",
      "17 cars",
      "15 cars"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 7,
      question: "Charlie had 8 fish and 6 of them died how much fish is left?",
      answer: "2",
      options: [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 8,
      question: "If James is 25 years and his sister is 3 years older than him , how old is his sister ?",
      answer: "28 yrs old",
      options: [
      "28 yrs old",
      "25 yrs old",
      "27 yrs old",
      "26 yrs old"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 9,
      question: "1 + 2 x 7",
      answer: "15",
      options: [
      "14",
      "7",
      "15.33",
      "15"
    ]
  },
    {
      numb: 10,
      question: "14/2 =",
      answer: "7",
      options: [
      "3",
      "4",
      "7",
      "6.5"
    ]
  },


  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];